RG 062:067, Town of Hebron
Connecticut State Library
Town of Hebron records
1797-1961
Connecticut State Library
Hebron (Conn.)
14 cubic feet
Administrative, tax, school, and election records for the town of Hebron.
RG062_067
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Hebron was incorporated on May 26, 1708.
Scope and Content
Administrative, tax, school, and election records for the town of Hebron.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Deeds -- Connecticut -- Hebron; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Hebron; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Hebron -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Hebron -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Hebron -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Hebron -- Registers
Places:
Hebron (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Accession: T000390, 1797-1907
  - Tax abstracts, including Andover and Gilead, 1797-1828 (Box Box 1)
  - Individual tax lists, 1819 (Box Box 2)
  - Abatements, 1800-1810 (Box Box 2)
  - Lists of property in First School District, 1866 (Box Box 2)
  - Town records, circa 1800-1900 (Box Box 2)
  - Including deeds, correspondence, school reports, and certificates of electors; lists of voters, 1906-1907 (Box Box 2)
  - Lists of voters, 1859-1872 (Map-case Map drawer 4)
- Accession: 2011-032, 1900-1961
  - Tax abstracts, 1900-1961
    - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908, 9 volumes (Box Box 1)
    - 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 9 volumes (Box Box 2)
    - 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 9 volumes (Box Box 3)
    - 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1935, 9 volumes (Box Box 4)
    - 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944, 9 volumes (Box Box 5)
    - 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949, 1950, 6 volumes (Box Box 6)
    - 1951, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1955, 1956, 6 volumes (Box Box 7)
    - 1957, 1958, 1959, 1960, 1961, 5 volumes (Box Box 8)
- Accession: T003296, 1862
  - United States tax assessment list for Division 16 of Collection District I, 1862; 1 volume (Volume Oversize item)
    Includes Andover, Bolton, Columbia and Hebron.